Chef P is the mad scientist behind the
pink sauce sludge that took the World by
storm last year a concoction so fell I
really thought there was a chance we'd
see the sequel to covid with this one I
really thought if people like ate the
pink sauce they just start dropping dead
from botulism and I think we were pretty
close but luckily a hero swooped in
called Dave's gourmet that purchased
pink sauce from Chef Pee and vowed to
actually make it edible and not
poisonous so
pink sauce lady was able to take a
disaster with this sauce and find
Success Through Dave's gourmet who then
put it in Walmarts across the United
States however since then Chef P has
made
unbelievably incomprehensibly bad
decisions I think she is so bad at
business that she will be studied for
the next 100 years for how hard she has
fumbled this whole thing and she just
continues to make it worse she just gets
worse and worse I've made like two
updates to her story over the last year
because it just the clown show never
stops with her she had the GoFundMe
recently and now she's waged the very
public war against Dave's gourmet
claiming they defrauded her she
acknowledges that Dave's gourmet did pay
her a hundred and twenty thousand
dollars but she [\h__\h] blew that all on
airbnbs and hotels apparently I guess
it's it's such a wacky story but she's
saying that Dave Gourmet is a bunch of
Scoundrels that you know took money and
didn't pay her what but she was owed
this and that and Dave's gourmet has now
responded to all the claims with their
information about what the terms of
their agreement were the payments and
all of that in order to combat the
claims that Chef P is waging against
them now I went over it on stream but I
couldn't pull up the official response
from Dave's gourmet for some reason so
instead I got just the bullet point
breakdown from a live Journal account
which side note I had no idea live
Journal still existed it was like seeing
an old friend such a blast from the
[\h__\h] past to see that live Journal
still exists okay so here they're just
breaking down
Dave's gourmet revealed that Veronica
received forty five thousand dollars up
front for purchasing the pink sauce
brand from her it was agreed that she
would be responsible for handling all
refunds to customers who receive bad
product or didn't receive anything
despite paying paying for it prior to
the partnership after the agreement was
signed it turns out Miss Shaw
did not have enough money to cover all
refunds so Dave's gourmet gave her
another thirty thousand to cover refunds
even though it was not their
responsibility
in Fall of 2022 Shaw was struggling
financially so Dave's gourmet provided
Shaw with multiple cash Advantage
advances that totaled more than forty
thousand dollars they did not charge her
any interest or fees these advances were
supposed to be offset by the future
royalties that Shaw was going to earn
oh my God she requested a ten thousand
dollar marketing expense to throw
herself a birthday party to maybe be
featured on Tick Tock she also requested
they pay for a dress 800 in shoes six
hundred dollars
she's she's insane she's an actual
lunatic
that is so quirky
and now she goes on Tick Tock daily
talking about how Dave [\h__\h] her now
she can't afford to have a house or feed
her children even though they were more
than generous here
like extremely generous
I don't know how you blow through all of
that money in the matter of six months
but that is shameful
Shaw attempted to submit business
expense reports for personal expenses
like buying four pairs of sneakers or
expensing her grocery bills Dave's
gourmet informed her that such
activities were fraudulent how dumb is
she how can someone actually be that
dumb it's Dave's gourmet he's not your
dad like he's not just gonna cover every
single one of your bills just because he
bought your [\h__\h] scam ass pink sauce
your biological weapon that you are
bottling
he bought your revolting potion for some
reason which was a terrible business
decision from Dave's gourmet to begin
with and now she's just trying to suck
as much juice out of the tank as she can
here
what in the world and yeah no she she
blew through all of this in like six
months
she went live talking about here you
know I'll just pull up her Tick Tock
again
talking about how she's homeless can't
feed her children and Dave's gourmet the
hundred twenty thousand dollars they
gave her was an installments and she
spent it all on airbnbs and hotels I
guess she literally went into diamond
and gold-plated airbnbs in order to
spend that much in six months
but she is beyond irresponsible
she has only herself to blame for
everything that's happened here
is this this is a piece of it but I
don't think it's the whole thing this is
what she talks about for sure these
people defrauded me so I will have to
sue them for a fraud because it's not
only the calculation of the royalty but
it's everything else
everything else like paying for your
birthday party of ten thousand dollars
plus including your dress and shoes
you started the GoFundMe which for some
reason Kyrie Irving donated twenty four
thousand dollars to
actual brain dead decision but I mean
money means nothing to him
so she'll get to throw herself another
birthday party with that money and then
complain again on Tick Tock live
I'm not lying here look
if you go to her GoFundMe which is still
up
you can see the donations
Kyrie Irving is right here 24 240 a
month ago
he's sugar daddying her
so that money is going right in the
[\h__\h] that's gonna be maybe like five
pairs of shoes that she's gonna blow
that one on I guess
she actually got to experience
some of the luckiest set of
circumstances a human being can have
just in her kitchen cooking up some
Wicked Alchemy makes the pink sauce it
goes viral on Tick Tock people buy it
out the ass
and she delivers poison
she basically tries to assassinate
people via postage with their pink sauce
and then even in spite of that she was
able to snatch Victory from the jaws of
defeat by getting bought by Dave's
gourmet and then she still fumbled that
it's impressive it's actually impressive
so first of all I want to acknowledge
this one hundred and twenty thousand oh
I bet she puts it in quotes even though
that's exactly what it was saying that
they paid me so number one
it wasn't an upfront payment of a
hundred and twenty thousand dollars
straight forward it was it was sent to
me partially
I don't know if it blocked out right
there because the low battery thing came
but it they were partial payments and
then also a huge chunk of that money
went towards me paying for Airbnb and
paying for hotels because my job I was
homeless for six months so that's where
all of the money apparently went which I
think is impossible even if you chose
the top line airbnbs and hotels you
would not blow through 120
000 [\h__\h] dollars in six months it
just wouldn't happen
that is unbelievably Reckless
so that is a blatant bold face lie Shaw
communicated that she had spent the
entirety of her previous advances and
that she needed another advance to feed
her children and to avoid being evicted
Dave's gourmet sent her two advances
that totaled 5K this seems honestly
everything that's happened with this
lawsuit makes Dave's gourmet seem like a
[\h__\h] Saint like an absolutely
beautiful place and business partner
they just keep giving her money because
they're buying into her lies she is not
spending [\h__\h] on her children or
anything besides herself and they keep
sending her money and then she keeps
being such an [\h__\h] to them
she had a party on a yacht and tried to
flex on Tick-Tock no way there's just no
shot she had a party on a yacht
let me see now I have to check that
claim she I don't even think she'd be
that dumb
because Dave Gourmet would see that
another thing she whined about was that
she had to do or pay for all the
marketing herself here let me give you a
peek at her super expensive marketing
for the pink sauce
just take a video of Pink sauce on some
food nothing else
actually nothing else
does that cost zero dollars
yeah I don't see the yacht you're
referring to though
in June of 2023 Shaw submitted an
expense report to Dave's gourmet that
included requests for payment for her
time dedicated to making social media
content such requests were outside of
the terms of the agreement Dave's
gourmet then asked for clarifications
related to the various expenses listed
by Shaw but backups receipts and
explanations were not provided
what a shocking development there
she didn't provide any proof of the
things she was claiming the money was
being used on
not not because
that wasn't being used by what she was
saying just because
[\h__\h] you
why don't you trust her
Miss Shaw had certain obligations in her
contract related to social media
activities that she violated multiple
times but Dave's gourmet chose not to
enforce them as to not create a strained
relationship
I didn't think she could make herself
look like more of an [\h__\h] than the
time she was on the uh the caramo show
interview where she condensed
condescending Jesus condescendingly
talked to that lady who was just
concerned about her health with pink
sauce
but yet somehow she found a way
she looks like an even bigger [\h__\h]
now
this company did not even force her to
abide by the contract she signed because
they didn't want to have a bad
relationship with her and then she goes
and burns the bridge anyway publicly she
started all this by the way it wasn't
Dave's gourmet she is the one that blew
the lid off of this with all the hoopla
in total Veronica Shaw received over a
hundred twenty thousand dollars in
payments from her partnership with
Dave's gourmet and pink sauce since
August of 2022 to date Davis Gourmet
offered to pay her attorney fees to go
over her contract to make sure all
payment she has received are in fact
correct but she declined
he's just been brain rotted by Tick Tock
she really thinks if she just whines and
cries on Tick Tock somehow the big bad
Dave's gourmet is going to give her even
more money that she doesn't deserve
they did so much for her far more than
any reasonable sane person or company
would ever do for somebody
and it still wasn't enough for her
gluttony
that pink sauce was toxic to her mind
she truly got lost in the sauce